http://www.arbutussoftware.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

Our Privacy Policy
At Arbutus Software, we take your privacy very seriously. Because of this, we want to provide you with explicit information on how we collect, gather, and identify information during your visit to our site. This information may be expanded or updated as we change or develop our site. For this reason, we recommend that you review this policy from time-to-time to see if anything has changed. Your continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of our privacy policy.
Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name, phone number, email or postal address. In many cases, we need this information to provide the personalized or enhanced service that you have requested.
The amount of personally identifiable information that you choose to disclose to Arbutus Software is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you provide it to us in conjunction with one of our services.
What information do we collect and how do we use it? Arbutus Software collects information on our users by your voluntary submissions (e.g., when you sign up for a white paper or request product information). We also collect, store and accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of this web site, such as which of our pages are most visited.  The information Arbutus Software collects is used in a variety of ways: for internal review; to improve the content of the site, thus making your user experience more valuable; and to let you know about products and services of interest.
Arbutus Analytics is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy, and we’ll only use your personal information to administer your account and to provide the products and services you requested from us. We would like to contact you about our products and services, as well as other content that may be of interest to you.
Email: If you have provided us your email address, Arbutus Software periodically sends promotional emails about products offered by us.  You can unsubscribe from these communications at any time.  We are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
You can unsubscribe at any time. If you do not wish to receive email information from Arbutus Software, please let us know by emailing us at unsubscribe@arbutussoftware.com or by writing us at:
#270-6450 Roberts StreetBurnaby, BCCanada V5G 4E1
Arbutus Software does not sell, rent, or give away your personal information to third parties.
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of the information described in this Privacy Policy by Arbutus Software.
Feedback
We welcome your questions and/or comments. Please send all queries to info@arbutussoftware.com..
#7b7c7f
#fff
TRY ARBUTUS
Request our fully functional free evaluation, and experience enhanced analytics performance firsthand.
REQUEST TRIAL
#fff
SCHEDULE A WEB DEMO
Find out how Arbutus data analysis technology can help your organization in a 20-minute web demo.
© Arbutus Software Inc.
